shots.me 2015-09-06

# Shots — Privacy Policy

## Effective Date: March 26, 2013

## Last Updated: March 4, 2014

SHOTS (“SHOTS MOBILE, INC.,” “us” or “we”) values the privacy of our users, members, and others (collectively or individually “Users”) who visit and use www.shots.com and its associated websites and services (collectively, the “Shots Site”). This statement governs information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of the Shots Site and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share, this information.

## The Information Shots Collects

### User Provided Information:

You may provide to Shots what is generally called “personally identifiable” information when you register, such as your name and e-mail address. In addition, Shots may give you the option to provide us with certain demographic information about yourself and to upload photographs or other personally identifiable information.

### “Cookies” Information:

When you visit the Shots Site, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer. Shots uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Shots Site. By using these cookies, we can “remember” what you have done on the Shots Site before and personalize our site for you. These persistent types of cookies can be removed. Each web browser implements different functionality, so please refer to the manuals or technical support resources that are available in conjunction with your web browser to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up. If you are using the Shots Site in a jurisdiction where your prior consent is required for us to deploy any particular cookies, you will be asked to accept such cookies before they are deployed. Please note that disabling cookies or declining to accept certain cookies will prevent you from accessing some of the functionality and site offerings available via the Shots Site.

### “Automatically Collected” Information:

When you visit the Shots Site or open one of our HTML emails, we may record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This “automatically collected” information may include your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Shots Site, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit.

## The Way Shots Uses Information

Shots uses the information that we collect to provide to you all of the features and services found on the Shots Site. We may use your email address for marketing purposes, unless you have expressly notified us that you prefer for us not to use your email address for any specific marketing purposes (“opt-out”). While you may opt-out from such marketing use, you may not opt-out from our use of your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes such as automatic notifications of recent account activity, or notifying you of major site updates.

Shots may use all of the information that we collect from our Users to understand the usage trends and preferences, to improve the way the Shots Site works and looks, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and to create new features and functionality.

As part of this process, we may use Google Analytics to provide us with aggregated information about how Users interact with the Shots Site, and may set cookies and/or use web beacons for this purpose. The information gathered by the Google Analytics software (including any personal information about you) will be sent to Google where it will be stored and used by Google in accordance with its own privacy policy rather than ours. Please review the Google Privacy Policy <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/> or contact Google for more information.

Shots allows other users to view your name, other profile details and photographs should you provide this information and make it publicly viewable.

Shots may use automatically collected information and cookies information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Shots Site; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed.

Shots will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional or marketing messages except for those specific programs or features for which you will have the ability to opt-out.

## When Shots Discloses Information

Shots may disclose both personally identifiable and automatically collected information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to process such information on our behalf, to provide website maintenance and security, to offer certain features on the Shots Site, to assist us in improving the way the Shots Site works and looks, and to create new features. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and we require these parties to use any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Shots may share automatically collected and other aggregated non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties for their use and distribution for their business purposes, including without limitation for the purposes of assisting them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, and promotions.

We may share personally identifiable information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent, except with respect to any specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-out.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with laws or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, warrants or other legal demands or to establish or defend Shots from legal claims; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties from fraud, abuse or violations of the Terms of Service or illegal acts; or (c) to protect the safety or integrity of Shots, its users, the public or other parties as it is deemed appropriate, in our sole discretion. You hereby consent to our sharing your personally identifying information under the circumstances described herein.

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, Shots does not share personal information about Users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a User’s request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Shots’ interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

## User Profile and Password

You have access to your personal information and you may update, correct, or delete your member information and email preferences at any time.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting Users profile access. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

PLEASE NOTE THAT WITH THE EXCEPTION OF CERTAIN CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION AS IDENTIFIED BY Shots FROM TIME TO TIME, ALL INFORMATION THAT YOU POST FOR VIEWING ON THE Shots SITE IS MADE PUBLICLY AVAILABLE TO ALL USERS OF THE Shots Site.

## Children

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13). Any person who provides their personal information to Shots through the Shots Site represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the Shots Site is directed to children under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided us with personally identifiable information without your consent, you may alert us at [privacy@shots.com](mailto:privacy@shots.com). If we learn that we have collected any personally identifiable information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Shots Site provides you with the opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about you. Shots Site gives you the option to end our use of your information, and to cease receiving or otherwise having access to future communications or services.   

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Shots may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Shots Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear within the Shots Site. They may automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content.

Shots may provide personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. Also, please note that if an advertiser asks Shots to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Shots's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other ad servers or ad networks or their websites.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be illegally or improperly accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If Shots learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Shots Site or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Shots Site. Shots may post a notice on the Shots Site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Shots Site. Shots may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us via email at [privacy@shots.com](mailto:privacy@shots.com).

## Special Note to International Users

The Shots Site is hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Shots Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions, and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * • the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and
  * • the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES TREAT YOUR INFORMATION IN A MANNER THAT MAY BE SUBSTANTIALLY DIFFERENT FROM, AND LESS PROTECTIVE THAN, THE TREATMENT REQUIRED UNDER THE LAWS OF OTHER COUNTRIES AND JURISDICTIONS. IF YOU DO NOT WANT YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, YOU SHOULD NOT SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH US, OR MAKE USE OF THIS WEBSITE.

TO THE EXTENT ALLOWED BY THE LAW OF THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE ANY RIGHT YOU MAY HAVE TO REQUIRE US TO TREAT YOUR IDENTIFYING INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF ANY COUNTRY OR JURISIDICTION OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES. HOWEVER, THE FOREGOING WAIVER MAY NOT BE LEGALLY BINDING IN SOME COUNTRIES, SUCH AS THE MEMBER STATES OF THE EUROPEAN UNION. TO THE EXTENT IT IS NOT LEGALLY BINDING IN THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, THIS FOREGOING WAIVER DOES NOT APPY TO YOU.

## In the Event of Merger or Sale

If Shots should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information Shots receives from you through the Shots Site is an Shots asset and may be transferred to another party; however, in the event of such a transfer, we will require that the transferee agree to honor this Privacy Policy, as it applies to Users prior to the effective date of any such transfer, unless we are legally prohibited from doing so.

## Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

Shots reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason. Each time Company exercises such right, you shall be required to affirmatively accept the updated Privacy Policy, and if you fail to do so, you will no longer be able to access or use the Shots Site.

## Contacting Shots

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@shots.com](mailto:privacy@shots.com) or write to us at:

Wilson Sonsini Goodrich & Rosati   
Attn: Shots Mobile, Inc.  
12235 El Camino Real, Suite 200  
San Diego, California 92130
